So that it has become so good, wait sorry, there were several who questioned John's gift.
And I actually have to go in and defend you Jhon.
Because you misunderstand there were several who just wait so you received as a gift that he should take care of the home or your child or your child who is obvious he should do
It was not so, then you have misunderstood everything, ie Jhon and I share everything as much, but that was, for example, that I could throw in and only today I do not want to do anything I want to be serviced.
It was rather so or, for example, I take care of Ivy all day now, for example, for example, we divide it, for example when Jhon comes home from work then he takes care of Ivy.
Then he takes the lay.
It's so, but such a day.
Then, for example, it can be the way you take everything, you take everything and it is luxury, so whatever you say it is luxury.
No, you have taken out the entire banana and mashed it now no ivy.
No.
This one then, what happened to it?
Now you have to take it there and go with it a little.
Ivy is just as akward in my vlogs when she just sits and looks at you like Jhon was my latest vlog when I stood and made breakfast with Lifesum recipe.
Then Jhon stands like this in the background.
You just, you are exactly like Ian or Ivy, type in the camera.
It is actually great fun, but do you know what is we start this damn day.
We go and put Ivy for his nap, I sit down and work a little and then hear and fucking in amazement.
You will be so shocked now.
But then I'll go and exercise.
And this has not happened since I gave birth to children in principle so that today I will train and I love my PT Kalle.
So that we will probably come mostly Catcha up than to work out.
We will mostly tramp and flame, have fun and laugh.
It's kind of what our workouts usually go about, exactly.
But then we will do that.
But first and foremost NAP for Ivy.
In fact, I also want to say one thing, Ivy has basically said mom now for the first time, she says this.
Ma ma, she says, but she says mom, you understand that it is me and shouts.
For example, if she is in her lap on someone else.
Then you call up to mom, or how yes, you actually do it.
Now it is actually not just what I want to believe, but she has actually started that way.
There are several who just, God, she says mother.
And then I make sure she sleeps during that time, so it's good anyway.
And when he works in the office yes then I have her 100 % but it must actually be that I work 100 % and am a maternal leave 100 %.
I am not a maternity leave and withdraw money but I am a maternity leave because I have a child and am a mother, but you understand what I mean.
But yes, it is not so easy in that industry to have time off and be mom free unfortunately.
It doesn't really work the same way, huh
But we have nevertheless put it up well so that for us this arrangement works as well.
I don't know if I have a key with me and it is locked, of course.
Hi, I have no keys.
Bath for you then.
So, forgive me, this is always the way you know, I can stand out there, knock, knock or that you shit in me then because sometimes I start to feel that you do this just to resist.
You just have to learn, you come in when I want you to come in.
So he runs, Jhon now they will imagine that you are a controlling boyfriend that we have a toxic relationship and that I live in oppression.
Oh my God, I have fucking forgot to tell oh my fucking good you know what happened, so listen to this.
No wait.
It was so so, I and I and Ivy are home.
We are sleeping until 10 pm.
11. John has gone to work and then there at half past 12 when we go out.
Yes then I notice that we are not coming out for the door.
I don't know what has happened.
The lock has only been broken in some way as well.
For Jhon locks as usual in the morning so we don't get out, so we started getting like this nightmare scenario and just oh my good thinking if it starts to burn here and me and Ivy do not come out.
I panic so I can call locksmiths coming.
He gets my keys, it is also not possible to open from the outside.
It has broken so he can just break the entire door.
Yes, this party costs us SEK 5250, top and then I wonder, you can pull this on home insurance there are several of you who have said that you can draw this on home insurance, but I do not know.
In any case, it was sick that it was so damn expensive that it was such an expensive fucking cost, but there was nothing to wait for.
I had to come out and it was also a safety risk to open the door.
I have to get out of there.
It was so uncomfortable, but it went well anyway.
Here I and I and Ivy are alive, it did not start burning, but we are, however, SEK 5250 poorer.
Sick enough that it was so expensive.
But, now let's go in and see what Ivy does.
So I can say this, I hung with Ivy.
Then I just felt no, now I need a little refresh, so I went and did a spray tan.
So I haven't washed it yet, but so from it to this then.
Now we decided a little spontaneously that my dad and his girl Agnet.
Girl do you say so?
Girl or cohabiting, Mrs. are they married?
It's nothing to you honey, I think you're good as you are.
I tell you, I will beat Frödinges.
Challenge accepted.
Aj honey, you should always hit me on the butt.
Of course it's mine.
Now it was this destructive relationship again.
I shit in, you understand mine is mine.
Oh mine is mine too, you know, now he starts to say that I am his property here.
100 %, you haven't told me to lock you in here.
Wasn't it in this vlog I told you it.
Yes.
Exactly, should you behave or should I lock you in.
I'm kidding.
There are people who misunderstood.
I'm kidding, I had never locked in ready.
Or or?
He pulls that joke every time you just where is the joke Jhon I do not keep up with.
John, you can't stand and bake here now when I'm going to make food.
You're like a fly.
I wipes you away and then you come back.
Listen I told Jhon was with Ivy now I should make food.
Then he will promptly stand here now and make food or scrapbook.
And I was clear darling that I need this spac.
And now to the potato buns and then you should have this parm cushion and then you just take regular crème fraiche and then you take grated parmesan, so this finely grated parmesan.
And then I usually take garlic spices, salt, pepper and this is what you put like ... This is what you put as a base.
This is what you put as a base before you put like this shrimp, red onion onion before you put everything, then you put the parmesan cream.
So that's now what we do.
What do you do so now I have just mixed the crème fraiche, this kind of finely grated parmesan and now we take garlic powder and then salt and pepper.
Type was as much parmesan as it is crème fraiche, so you know it.
So it should really taste as well as cheese and garlic and salt and pepper.
Delicious.
Now it's time for the sauce and on New Year's Eve I had a funnel chanterelle and it was so damn good.
But now I didn't find it.
So now there are just ordinary mushrooms and then whipped cream and then a little crème fraiche as it gets so damn good.
And then I usually have in veal broth and some soy.
And I usually run on this one.
That veal broth.
And then just a little soy salt and pepper, and then we are at home.
And as I show, plain fucking cream and regular fucking crème fraiche.
Nothing like that where you know light cream fresh or something like that without ordinary creme fraiche to get this creamy.
I'm just saying, this sauce, divine.
The Lordship has come.
Ok, now I'm just about to jump into the shower.
Dinner is done.
Dad and Agneta have gone home and I just have to say your draft cake honey, wow.
No it was wow.
It was really good and the dinner became delicious.
I didn't actually film the meat and everything because you controlled you.
But no so it was a delicious dinner, very delicious and now I have to jump into the shower and we just have to see clear love island here which is.
So, I can only say one thing and that is that I hate Johnny, then.
I hate him.
No, i think he is so fucking ... what do you